theme-dutch.com 2019-05-01

# Themedutch | Privacy Policy

This is the privacy statement of Themedutch BV, registered in the Trade Register at the Chamber of Commerce under number 66503078 in the Netherlands. The privacy policy of Themedutch BV (hereafter “Themedutch”) has been established in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) of the European Union. Themedutch attaches great importance to the protection of your personal data and this privacy policy describes the processing of personal data in the organization as well as our website www.theme-dutch.com.

Themedutch knows how our clients and visitors like you value your privacy, and we have created this privacy policy to ensure that you understand our policies and procedures, what personally identifiable information you must provide if you wish to use the site and, ultimately, just how we use such personally identifiable information. This policy applies only to the website located at www.umswitcher.com, and not to any other website or service. If you do not agree with this policy, then you should not use the site. We do NOT sell or share names, email addresses, or any other personal information.  

## How we protect our website

Themedutch knows how our clients and visitors like you value your privacy, and we have created this privacy policy to ensure that you understand our policies and procedures, what personally identifiable information you must provide if you wish to use the site and, ultimately, just how we use such personally identifiable information. This policy applies only to the website located at www.theme-dutch.com, and not to any other website or service. If you do not agree with this policy, then you should not use the site. We do NOT sell or share names, email addresses, or any other personal information. How we protect our website:

SSL Connection  
24/7 365 monitoring  
Anti-DDoS  

## Personally identifiable information collected by Themedutch

Themedutch may collect and store personally identifiable information about you if you voluntarily submit such information to Themedutch. Personally identifiable information may include your name, email address, physical address and other information that specifically identifies you.  

## Processing personally indentifiable data

Themedutch processes personal data in accordance with the purpose for which they were provided. Themedutch processes the minimum amount of data needed for the specific purpose. For the processing of personal data Themedutch asks permission where necessary. Themedutch only processes personal data of minor persons under the age of 16, if the parent, caregiver or legal representative has given permission in writing. 

Themedutch only provides personal information to third parties if necessary for the purposes for which the were provided. We provide your personal data to third parties if we are obliged to do so on the basis of the law or a court decision.

Themedutch’s website is carful with information obtained through the website and will ensure that the processing of the data complies with applicable laws and regulations.

Themedutch has taken appropriate organizational and technical measures to ensure the protection of personal data. Themedutch is not responsible for the privacy policy of other sites, which are accessible through a link on our website. We recommend that you consult the privacy statement and disclaimer of that other website when accessing third party websites via our website.  

## Access to your personally indentifiable data

You have the right to inspect, rectify or delete your personal data at any time. In that case, you can contact us with the request to remove your personal data from our records. If your contact information should change, please contact us so that we can update our records accordingly. You can use the e-mail address on our contact page. To prevent abuse, we can ask you to identify yourself adequately. Themedutch does what’s possible to keep your personal details accurate and up-to-date. Please contact Themedutch if your details need to be changed so that we can update your details accordingly.  

## Storage personally indentifiable data

Themedutch stores personal data no longer than necessary for the realization of the purposes for which they were collected, processed or required by law.  

## Purposes processing personally indentifiable data

Themedutch collects personal data from customers and suppliers for: administrative obligations, carrying out and processing contractual agreements, communication about business transactions, communications about other relevant events or changes. 

Themedutch collects personal data from potential customers, interested parties and stakeholders for: administrative obligations, communications about products and services, communications about relevant events or changes. 

Themedutch collects personal data from employees for administrative obligations, employment contracts, digital communication systems and for the execution of assignments.  

## Technical and organizational measures

Themedutch has taken technical and organizational measures to protect all personal data.  
Themedutch restricts access to personal data by means of individual user rights. Themedutch uses username and password policy on all used systems. Themedutch makes back-ups of personal data in order to be able to recover these in case of physical or technical incidents. Themedutch monitors its systems and servers. Themedutch can anticipate in case of calamities.  

## Use of Cookies

We may use cookies and similar technologies to collect non-personally identifiable information from you and to customize your use of the site. A cookie is a small data file that certain web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies; however, you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent or you can flush your browser of cookies from time to time. (Note: you may need to consult the help area of your browser application for instructions.) If you choose to disable cookies or refuse to accept a cookie, you may not be able to utilize all features of the Site.

At times, some of our advertisers and their ad service providers set cookies when you click their advertising banners. While we use cookies in other parts of the site (as discussed above), cookies received with banner ads are collected by those advertisers and their ad service providers. The advertiser’s privacy policy and/or that of its service provider will govern the use of this information and Themedutch is not responsible for the privacy practices of such advertiser or ad service provider.  

## Links

The site may contain links to web sites maintained by third parties. Themedutch is not responsible for the privacy practices of such third party sites. You should carefully read their own privacy policies before providing any information to such third parties.  

## Opt out procedures

You have the option to opt in and also to opt out of receiving information from Themedutch. This opt out messaging will appear at the bottom of every promotional email that is sent out to you by themedutch in relation to this site and for which you opt in voluntarily. Themedutch also gives you the option to remove your information from its database of active users. If you no longer wish to take advantage of this Site or to receive any form of direct contact from THEME DUTCH, whether it is email, discounts, newsletters, or other promotional offers or materials, or wish us to delete your personally identifiable information from our database of active users, send us a request marked “Privacy-Urgent”, and contact us.

In order to ensure that the information we maintain is accurate, Themedutch gives users the option to change or modify their information previously provided. If you would like to change your information currently in our database, please contact us.  

## Security

We are committed to taking reasonable steps to ensure the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put into place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to help safeguard and secure the information we collect online. However, due to the inherent open nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and us or information stored on the site or our servers, will be completely free from unauthorized access by third parties such as hackers and your use of the site demonstrates your assumption of this risk.  

## The Netherlands

Our site is maintained in The Netherlands. By using the site, you freely and specifically give us your consent to export your personally identifiable information to The Netherlands and to store and use it in The Netherlands as specified in this policy.  

## Changes to this privacy policy

This privacy statement is subject to change without notice in case of changes to business operations of Themedutch. Therefore we advise to consult this privacy statement on a regular basis.  

## Contacting us

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, you can contact us.

In addition, our mailing address is: Themedutch BV  
Headquarters : Koningin Regentesselaan 44, 6043 CM ROERMOND

Effective Date: This privacy policy was last updated on May 21, 2018
